mkwhy.com 2014-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Men know why

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google** Adsense  
**Google** , as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of **DART** cookies by **Google** enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are **based** on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the **DART** cookies you may visit the **Google** ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the **DART** cookie mechanisms are subject to **Google** ’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to **track** users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

Collection of **Personal** Information  
When visiting , the **IP** address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and **times** of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, **track** users **movement** and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded **IP** addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links to third party Websites  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

Changes to this Privacy Statement  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
